All of Carrick View
is out of bounds.
Angela Mackle is OOB.
It's all the streets
where the McIntyres live.
Why would they be off limits to us?
There's enough bad things in life
that'll come looking for you. son.
You don't need to
go looking for them.
Angela?
Lough Point?
That must be nice up there.
Yeah. Yeah. yeah.
Mrs McIntyre. do you feel up
to answering a few questions?
See you brought the big crayon
tonight.
Do you mind. Constable?
I'm interviewing a victim here.
You a victim here. Tina?
Mm-hm.
Somebody mentions something
in a phone call. or...
Mentions they want to kill me?
Most of what you need to know
is in there.
I'm not worried about myself.
It's my mum.
Maybe it's time you left home.
James told me to give it to you.
It's your father's pension
from the organisation.
It's what we are entitled to.
Just take the money. Ma.
You get it from the usual place?
The Dublin lads. yeah.
I keep records of the drop-offs
and how much goes out.
Have you been dealing off base?
You are in big trouble. wee fella.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
OK.
Thank you.
Thanks. Cheers.
LOCAL RADIO IN BACKGROUND
THUDDING MUSIC FROM CAR
MUSIC BLARES
How's it going?
Yo.
We're on for tonight.
out the back of yours.
What time?
Whenever we're there.
Sorry. Spilt a bit.
CLOCK TICKS
FOOTSTEPS APPROACH
The kids are asleep.
They're in our room.
Good.
Here.
Get the whisky. would you?
FOOTSTEPS RECEDE
GLASSES CLINK
FOOTSTEPS APPROACH
Take it.
GRACE: Oh. shit.
You OK?
Er. yeah. Yeah. I'm fine.
I'm just tired.
Can't get used to these lates.
Yeah. it can't be easy at your age.
You what?
You cheeky bastard.
It is hard.
My son thinks I'm a ghost.
What age is he?
Er. he's 17.
He's doing his A levels.
I mean...
..I don't think
there's a worse time
I could be doing this.
You must have had him
when you were young.
Yeah.
You got kids?
No. no kids.
So. shall we...?
Shall we...? Yeah.
STEVIE YAWNS
You're tired too. Yeah.
GRACE LAUGHS
What a shithole.
I've been waiting for you
over two hours!
Er. Mr Wallace?
Doctor.
Oh. Doctor Wallace.
Can you tell us what happened?
I was asleep.
and I was woken by
the sound of the engine.
I jumped out of bed.
then I saw my car being
driven out of my driveway.
and not by me.
And I still have these.
Er...
so it's a Range Rover 50?
Registration DR 007?
Don't suppose it has
an ejector seat. does it?
HE CHUCKLES
I'm not sure I like your attitude.
Constable...
..Cliff.
Well...
..Doctor...
..I'm a wee bit like Guinness
in that way.
Acquired taste.
THEY CHUCKLE
I'll just go and radio this in.
GERRY WHISTLES
KNOCKING AT DOOR
SHE BREATHES RAGGEDLY
Come on. son.
Come on. Please.
Wait! Don't forget these.
You'll be OK. Look at me.
You'll be OK.
Come on. Junior.
Please. son.
Love you.
I have to stay here.
Just go with them.
and do as they say. all right?
I'm sorry. Da.
I know. son.
Fuck.
MAN: On the ground.
Face down.
You're OK. son.
JP JUNIOR: No. no. please.
I won't do it again!
Please! I'm sorry!
JP SENIOR SOBS
No. please. no.
No. please. please.
don't do this. Please!
No. please. please. don't!
No. please. stop!
PARENTS SCREAM
DOG BARKS
Junior! Junior!
Oh. son!
Siobhan! Siobhan!
HE SOBS
My wee boy!
SOBBING CONTINUES
LIQUID TRICKLES
Breathe. JP! Breathe. son!
SIRENS WAIL
They're coming now.
Up here!
Please!
JP JUNIOR WHIMPERS AND GASPS
Trauma kit. Trauma kit.
Help. please!
Stand back. please. sir.
Stand back. please.
He's been shot!
JP JUNIOR YELLS
It's burning. it's burning.
please!
STEVIE: Grace.
Hey! Trauma kit.
Going to tourniquet him.
OK. What's your name?
Don't let me die!
What is his name?
Same as me. It's JP.
All right. OK. JP. JP. JP.
You are OK. you're going to be OK.
all right?
JP. you're going to feel a burning
in your leg.
but that's a good sign. OK?
That's a good thing.
JP YELLS
No!
Get on to the ambulance. please.
Get an ambulance update.
JP GROANS
Uniform. Uniform. Bravo Lima 72.
Requesting ambulance ETA. Over.
RADIO: We have an ambulance. Should
be with you any minute now. Over.
Keep a bit of pressure on that.
Grace. please.
JP WHIMPERS
JP?
No. JP. JP. open your eyes. You...
Don't close your eyes. OK?
Look at me. JP.
SIOBHAN: JP!
JP SENIOR: Siobhan!
No! Siobhan. no! No!
I want to see him!
Get back. Stay back. Get back!
SIREN WAILS
I want to see him!
Get back in the house!
I want see him. my boy!
What did they do to my boy?!
GRACE: He's going to be OK.
He's getting...
Get off me!
It's my son! Please!
Let's get in here. Come on.
JP. can you hear me?
What have they done to him?
JP. you're doing good. kid.
RAGGED BREATHING
What's your relation to him?
I'm his da. JP...
Keep talking to him.
Try and keep him awake. please.
You're going to be OK. Stay awake.
big man. come on.
Let go! I want to see him!
He's going to be all right.
Just get inside. OK?
Right. Er... Look. can you
tell me what happened?
What happened?! My son was shot!
No. I know. I understand...
Look. I understand
how difficult this must be.
but can you tell me...
..how it happened?
We heard the shots.
My husband ran outside
and I stayed here
with the younger kids.
OK.
You see. er. we received calls
from a few of the residents
reporting the shooting at 9:39pm.
and you called five minutes later.
Why such a delay?
Because my son had just been shot!
We were a wee bit busy.
you know?
Was this done by appointment?
Did you know they were coming?
I've nothing more to say about it.
DOORBELL
FOOTSTEPS APPROACH
How are you. love?
What are you doing here?
Ah. just...
..thought I'd call in and say hello.
You got the place looking well.
Gordy told me you didn't take
your allowance this month.
that you'd given it back.
I just don't want to take it
any more. OK?
Listen...
..I want to talk to you about
all that roaring and shouting
you were doing in the street the
other day. It's bad news. love.
I know things haven't been easy
for you.
God knows we all know that.
but bringing the police
around here like that...
..it's not on.
And then you take a lift home
from a peeler.
That's just dangerous. love.
Now. I've been looking
after you and the wee lad.
like I promised Rory I would.
but even I have my limits.
Now. any more of this rubbish
from you
and I won't be looking
after either of you any more.
In fact...
..I'll be doing
the exact opposite.
FOOTSTEPS RECEDE
DOOR OPENS
Put that on. I don't want
to get blood on the car.
Come on. you were
a social worker. you've never
dealt with stuff like this before?
Yeah. no. I have. but not like that.
Not up close.
AMBULANCE REVERSING BEEPS
Well. you'll get used to it.
Catch the shite.
empty the bucket. repeat.
No.
No. Stevie. we can do better
than that.
Come on.
HE COUGHS
Right?
Story. bud?
Yeah. good.
All went OK.
Come here to me. you. yeah?
CLEARS THROAT
There's an extra 5% in that batch.
So we're good for last time. yeah?
Mm.
Something else I want
to chat to you about.
ENGINE REVS
HE COUGHS
INAUDIBLE
Look. can I talk to him? Alone?
Well. when that happens.
I usually have to explain
things to a senior officer.
HE SIGHS
OK. I'll go and get a coffee.
Do you mind if I sit?
How are you doing?
He'll be OK.
Look. what the doctors
won't tell you
is that when JP wakes up.
he will probably be happy.
He'll be relieved that
it wasn't as bad as he thought.
And in a week or two...
..he might go quiet.
Your doctor...might prescribe
him antidepressants
to go with the painkillers.
but you really need
to keep an eye on him.
OK?
It will be the physiotherapy that's
the hardest. though. because...
..well. because...
..that's when he might realise
that he...
..he might not walk properly
again. or...
..or ride a scooter.
He might say he hates you for it.
Hates me?
For allowing it to happen.
I didn't...
No. look. I'm not blaming you.
I'm not blaming you. I know...
I know how it works.
I think you're a man who's been
given a terrible choice.
They either put a bullet
in his head
or in his knee.
That was it. wasn't it?
Would you make a statement for us?
You're not in England any more.
love.
You don't just run around touting to
the peelers just because...
What. because somebody tried
to shoot your child?
Look...
..I'm not from here.
but I have lived here
for 20 years.
20 years. huh?
Well. you should know by now
that if I give a statement.
they're coming back.
only this time they're not
aiming for his knees.
Nor mine.
Constable Ellis?
DS Canning.
You're off shift. so
what are you doing here?
Well. I was first responder
at the scene.
The mother. she was worried.
and the father wasn't
answering his phone. so...
Right.
I'll take it from here.
Just send me through
the paperwork in the morning.
will you?
Mr Whelan. I'm DS Murray Canning.
I'll be leading this investigation.
I'm very sorry to hear
what's happened.
Would you mind coming in with me
to the next room to talk this over?
THUD
Jesus. Annie!
I nearly shot you. Ma!
You told me you'd quit!
Well. I had. During the day.
What are you doing with that?
There's... There's something
I need to tell you.
What was all that about
with you and Sully?
Oh. we were talking about...
Mind your own fucking business!
GORDY: Which car are we?
This is us.
You're messing.
Ha!
You're driving. I am wrecked.
Fuck.
JOSEPH: So Det South picked up
the vehicle
crossing the border
early this morning.
Overt and covert cameras.
in combination
with our operator. surveilled it
to this scrapyard in Moylough.
Vehicle was stripped and drugs
removed to a second vehicle.
You had the whole trip
under surveillance?
OK. um. what now?
The Ginleys are a major
European crime syndicate.
This could be our way into that.
HE SCOFFS
This has to stop somewhere.
I mean...
..it can't go on for ever.
My people are starting to talk.
Let them talk.
Inspector. the work that we do
is what keeps your officers
alive.
How many murder plots
have we interrupted
in the last three years because of
information from Farset?
We're not asking for thanks.
but we are asking to be
left alone to do our job.
And it's your responsibility
to ensure that that happens.
All right. Ma?
You two. in the kitchen.
Right. Tina?
Look like you want to count it.
You saying I don't trust you?
Go and make us a cup of tea.
I'll have a cup too. Gordy.
Sit down.
I meant you.
FORK CLANGS
Does Gordy want one?
No. I'm fine. thanks.
Take a cup of tea.
Milk and two sugars.
DOORBELL
Gordy didn't come home
last night. and...
..I heard someone was
kneecapped. I'm so worried.
Jesus fuckin' wept!
Gordy!
Get that woman
away from my house.
Gordy!
MUTTERS: For fuck's sake.
Gordy. what are you doing
in this house?
What do you want? I told...
Go home. Seriously.
What?!
What are you doing here?
I told you not to come here.
Just go home!
I'm just...
What did I say to you?!
I'm just... I'm just here
to get Gordy. Gordy. please.
I'm not a wean any more. Just
fucking go home. seriously.
You don't know
what you're doing here.
Why are you doing this to him?
Why are you doing this to him?!
Stop. Why...?
That's it!
Why are you doing this to him?!
Get off of me! Go on.
Get off of me!
Go. Go on!
Fuck!
Gordy! Gordy. come back with...
Go on.
DOOR CLOSES
Well. that's OK.
We'll just do what it says
here. and...
..and it'll be fine.
Sure nobody about here
wants to hurt you.
Ma...
Why would anybody
want to hurt you?
Ma. it's like...
And all they give us
is a bloody leaflet!
You don't have to do this job.
You know that?
Ma...
But if you go.
what am I going to do without you?
I know.
SHE SNIFFS
Hey. missus.
You OK?
Mm-hm.
SHE SNIFFS QUIETLY
Annie?
Hey!
Hey. hey. hey.
What's going on?
Hmm?
What's happened?
SHE MOUTHS
It's OK.
Hey. Cal. buy me these crisps.
Go on. Buy your own crisps.
Ugh. what are you like?
A wee party hat?
Suits you.
£3.20.
Thank you.
Sorry.
Need to look into your bag.
Who?
You.
You what?
I need to look in your schoolbag.
Look. I just paid. mate.
Leave him alone.
He didn't steal anything.
You stay out of it.
I need to check your bag.
All right.
Away you go.
Why'd you do that? Just leave it.
mate. No. I want to know
why he picked you.
Fucking leave it. OK? Come on.
Man. screw that guy.
We'll go back in and rob him.
Hi.
Er. here are our statements
and notebook entries for last night.
Thanks.
Um. for what it's worth.
I think the dad might talk.
I mean. out of all of them.
in terms of a statement.
The dad might talk?
Well. yeah.
Yeah. I think it's possible.
I mean. I spoke with him at the
hospital last night and I think
there's part of him that really
wants to nail these bastards
for what they did.
TOILET FLUSHES
You still here?
You think I'm some blow-in.
don't you.
who doesn't know
what she's up against?
Let me just think for a second.
Yeah.
Do you know I've lived
in Belfast for 19 years?
And I was a social worker
for ten of those.
So I know
what I'm talking about.
OK. Well...do you know how
many punishment shootings
there were here
in the last calendar year?
43.
Do you know how many
convictions we got?
Zero.
Do you know how many witness
statements we managed to get.
including from the victims?
Zero.
So you're only in the door.
and you think
you can get a collar
on a punishment shooting.
which is what none of us
have been able to do
in at least ten years.
Is that about right?
Yeah. Yes. it is.
And they're no longer referred
to as punishment shootings.
They are called
paramilitary-style attacks.
because the term
"punishment shooting"
implies that the victim
deserves it. and I don't think
that a 15-year-old kid
deserves that.
Do you?
HE SCOFFS
Well. come on. then.
This I have to see.
MUSIC BLASTS FROM RADIO
TURNS RADIO OFF
RADIO: 74 from Uniform. Over.
Bravo Lima 74. Over.
We're getting calls about
a semi-naked man who's
locked himself on a bus. Over.
Is this a wind-up?
I hope not. 74. Sounds like
a good one. Over.
SHE TURNS SIREN ON
74 responding. Over! Jesus!
What a beautiful city.
ladies and gentlemen!
SIREN WAILS
What a gem!
WHOOPING
I think you'll agree.
Look outside these buildings
and you will see the majestic
beauty of the Belfast Hills
rolling down to the sea.
And nestled in between them...
He waited until we all got off the
bus. then he locked the doors
behind us. You have to get him down.
I'll get the sack for this!
..full
of the friendliest people...
Prick!
..in the whole world!
And here we have
our two local police officers.
who are also. I may say.
the nicest...
Right. we'll need
to get him down.
Yeah. no shit. Jen.
Obviously. like.
..on God's Earth.
Aren't you. girls?
Sir. you've had your fun.
Come on. I need you
to get your clothes on
and get down here immediately.
or you'll be arrested.
So. now. ladies and gentlemen.
let me tell you a wee bit more
about Belfast.
What has he done?
He's locked it from the inside.
Fuck's sake.
Did you know that this is
one of the few places on Earth where
nothing bad has ever happened?
Sir? You've been warned. I need
you to come down now. please.
I'm going to tell you
the real truth
about our history.
CHEERING
No. we don't want to know.
It's just everybody...
Sir?
..pissing over everybody else
for hundreds of years.
Just one big flowing
river of pish!
BYSTANDERS CHEER
Sorry about your bus here. What do
you mean you're sorry about my bus?!
GLASS SMASHES
You do not need to say anything.
but I must caution you
that if you do not mention
when questioned
something you later rely on
in court.
it might harm your defence.
Turn around.
No. Hands.
If you do say anything.
it may be given in evidence.
Do you understand the caution?
I do. love. and thanks
a million. Appreciate it.
You appreciate being arrested?
Are you for real?
Come on! Let's get down to
the station. get me processed.
Come on! Let's do it.
Come on.
CHEERING
BUZZER
WOMAN: Yeah?
Hello.
I was wondering
if I could speak with
Constable Grace Ellis. please.
Let me just check.
I'm sorry.
she's not currently on duty.
Is there anyone else
who can help you?
Do you know when
she'll be back at work?
I'm sorry. but we can't divulge
that information.
See that number plate up front?
That's actually an old one.
1987. Not many of those around now.
Worth a few bob. that one.
Pull over.
What?
Happy Kelly.
I'm de-arresting you.
You what?
You're what?!
There's no way I'm ruining
my arrest record on this.
Your arrest record?
Are you joking me?
They won't even put him in a cell.
They'll send him straight home
and send us straight back
on patrol again.
It's pointless.
No. please.
It's fine. Please. arrest me.
What?!
I...
HE SIGHS
I just don't want to be
on my own today.
That's all.
I get it.
I understand.
You just want to spend time
with someone.
Anyone. Don't you?
But the only way
we are absolutely
obligated to stay with you
and look after you
is if you tell us
you're feeling suicidal.
What?
Jen...
Are you?
Suicidal?
Jen. what the fuck?
Well...
..I mean...
Cos...
..if you tell me that you are.
we'll have to take you
to hospital
and stay with you
until you receive
appropriate medical attention.
I can do that
now I've de-arrested you.
instead of going
to the police station.
And we'll have to stay with you
at the hospital.
That's the rules. Jen. you can't
deliberately...
Yeah. I am. actually.
I...think I'm going to
kill myself.
That's what I thought.
I can't fucking believe this.
You heard what he said.
Hospital. please. Constable Conlon.
Those are the rules.
Don't worry. This'll take ages.
ENGINE STARTS
Class.
They must've jumped
the wrong fella.
Anyways. it's no big deal.
Did they say something to you
to make you think
that they thought
you were someone else?
No.
How long have you worked
for the McIntyres?
Excuse me?
Well. you know.
you ride around Carrick View
on that new scooter of yours.
Are you a delivery boy? Hmm?
What. did you lose a package?
Did you steal a package?
Fuck you. peeler.
Hey! Watch your mouth!
What did you do
that was so wrong
that they did this to you?
You need to stop this now.
Constable Ellis.
Yeah.
Yeah. yeah. OK.
OK.
Yeah. but we have
to be honest here
and ask.
where does all of this get you.
this pretending?
Because you're pretending
that you're OK.
and that you can deal
with this. but let me tell you.
when that adrenaline wears off.
it is going to be really hard.
And you're having to pretend
that you don't know
who did this or why.
And. yes. maybe...
..maybe I'm naive
and I'm pretending that I can
do something about it. but...
..who does
all of this protect?
Because it's not you. JP.
And it's not your mum. and
it's not those two little boys
that are coming up behind you.
The only people
that this protects
are the bastards
that did this to you.
Right. OK.
BACKGROUND CHATTER
Ah! There she is.
Constable Robinson.
You're a treasure.
There you go.
Well. might as well make
ourselves comfortable
since we've got
such a long wait. huh?
Oh. look! It's actually
getting longer.
Hey!
Excuse me.
I know you think you know us.
the type of people we are.
but you don't.
We didn't know he was
dealing for the McIntyres.
Knew he was keeping with
the wrong company. yes.
but not that. Then he thought
he was smarter than them.
Thought he'd worked out a way
to make an extra few bob.
Instead of selling the stuff
they give him
around the estate. he took it
to South Belfast.
charged double.
When that bad batch came through.
that's when they found out.
And the night he told us.
he was crying his eyes out.
I...
I work in a garage on
the Floralhall Road. you know?
You get all sorts in there.
Drugs. thieves.
I've even been held up
by a lad with a knife once.
That's why the CCTV cameras
in there are so good.
What was that about?
I think there's going to be
something on the CCTV footage
at his work.
On the night of the shooting.
DOOR OPENS
Hey.
I'm sorry again
for staying late.
Did you get something to eat?
OK. come on. Spit it out.
What?
Well. what's wrong with you
these days?
Nothing.
Listen. I am sorry
that I've been so busy at work.
It's just I have
to get through this probation
period. and then I can...
I know. I know. it's fine.
You have to work. I get it.
Well. what is it. then. Cal?
Because if there's something
bothering you. I need to know.
I'm thinking about...changing
my first preference.
For the uni applications.
But...
..I thought you were going
to stay here.
Go to Queen's. Isn't that
what we talked about?
I'm thinking about England.
London...Manchester. maybe.
OK. Well. that...
That sounds expensive.
I'd work to pay my living expenses.
You wouldn't have to worry about it.
Oh. come on. Cal. that's not
what I meant. Well. what. then?
What's wrong with me wanting
to spread my wings a bit? Or do I
have to spend the rest of my life
living here with you?
Cal!
Cal. come on. I didn't mean...
HE RUNS UPSTAIRS
DOOR SLAMS
That is an entire shift
spent sitting on our arses.
What an achievement.
Here to serve.
How the fuck
do you get away with it?
Oh. sorry.
Sorry. I almost forgot.
Your ma runs the place.
Well. not quite.
But...yeah. nearly.
Seriously. though.
Why be a police officer
if you hate it so much?
And do you not care
what people think of you. like?
Well. first of all.
I'm not going to be
in response policing
for very much longer.
Certainly not in this section.
And as for what people
think of me.
why would I care about that?
Good to go.
Make sure he gets home safe. yeah?
We will do. Yeah. Thank you. Doctor.
Thanks. All right. come on.
Home time.
JAMES: What do you think?
GORDY: Yeah. it's...
..it's amazing.
I thought you could move in here.
Spread your wings a wee bit.
Save me having
to bring a tenant in.
What?
Me? In here?
You'd be paying rent. mind you.
But. yeah. Why not?
You can't live with your ma
for ever. can you?
DOORBELL
Oh! Can I help? Sorry. I actually
might be on the wrong street here.
Is this. er...?
I'm actually just...
I'm looking for... Annie!
Hey! Annie!
I am sorry.
Er. Cal. yeah. I was going to
mention it earlier.
but you were. er...busy.
Annie is a colleague of mine.
She's going to stay
for a few days until she finds
a place of her own. She didn't
tell me you were this handsome.
ALL LAUGH
Right. come on.
Oh. cheers. Grace.
OK. You're a life-saver.
Maybe literally.
Yeah...
Right.
OK. Let's get some glasses.
Terrible drouth on me.
If you admit that
you're brutally hungover...
..you can have
this bacon bap...
..and this mug of coffee.
Yeah. all right. Yeah.
I admit it.
Sometimes you need good food.
Sometimes you need nasty food.
Oh. God. I need nasty food.
Oh. will you plug my phone in
for me? It's almost dead.
Your phone's not the only one.
Ha-ha.
What's that?
It's the CCTV footage
we requisitioned last night.
It's from the petrol station
where JP Senior works.
Who?
The dad. Of the lad
that was shot in the knee.
Murray asked me
to take a look at it.
Oh. Murray did. did he?
What?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Oh. my God.
Three hours
before the shooting.
It's not a slam dunk.
but it's definitely something.
Is this the part where you get
to say. "I told you so"?
HE CHUCKLES
We're on patrol in 15.
Everything all right?
Yeah. no. I'm fine. Yeah.
Well. go on. then.
What?
Look under it.
I'll see you tonight. then.
Yep.
OK. Er...
Cell 12. please. Thank you.
Come on. mate. Follow me.
All right. sexy?
Go on. get lost.
You have the right
to remain sexy.
but I must caution you that...
I haven't seen one
as green as that in a while.
They get more clueless
every year.
He's got me thinking. though.
He was comparing
the OOB calls
with serious crime reports.
There's a lot of overlaps.
Like. too many.
Jesus. Gerry.
I'm just saying.
Don't say it.
And don't think it.
Have you learned nothing
in 27 years?
This is exactly the sort of
thing that got you into trouble
in the first place.
Seriously. Gerry. leave it.
You just wait
till I get you home.
HE GROWLS SEDUCTIVELY
Go on. piss off. you knobhead.
HE GROWLS
SHE LAUGHS
Listen. we're going to have
to borrow her for an hour.
I've cleared it with
Sergeant McNally.
Are you joking me?
She's the one who has the
relationship with the witness.
So. what. I should just go and
read the papers or something?
You can read?
Right. come on.
Let's go
and get this over with.
I'll see you.
So if it's enough.
use it to go after them.
Well. it might not be enough.
Look. it's strong
circumstantial evidence.
and a jury
will be swayed by it. but...
SHE SIGHS
But with a statement from you.
JP. explaining that this was
them setting up a time
for the shooting. then it would
be legally compelling.
No.
We've been through this.
No statements.
They'll have us fucking killed!
Look...
..if you indicate
that you're even willing
to give a statement.
we can look into getting you
some financial support.
to help you relocate
somewhere safer?
Oh. aye?
Where?
I know where.
My sister Clodagh.
She lives down in County Mayo
with her family.
They have a hotel there.
No.
Love...
No. No!
Shit. we don't even know
if they'll have us!
They will. I've asked her.
You've asked her?!
Fuck!
Your son is lying up in that
hospital. full of painkillers.
And why?
Because we let it happen.
Us. JP.
We might as well
have pulled the trigger.
HE SIGHS
And what's next. huh?
What about Lorcan and Ciaran?
Are they next?
Give them what they want.
I'll start packing.
Siobhan...
Siobhan!
DOORBELL
FOOTSTEPS ON STAIRS
Did you forget something. Annie?
So. it looks like
we might just be able
to prosecute a punishment...
..a paramilitary-style assault.
Miracles do happen.
Not today. they don't.
What happened?
Well. they aren't proceeding
in the case against
Mo McIntyre and Gordy Mackle.
It's not in the public interest.
Is that right?
Yeah.
You know. but the family still
have to move away. though.
They gave a statement.
The security risk
is too high.
and they have to move.
I've just made this family move
away from everything they know.
take their kids. for what?
Hmm? Hmm?
For nothing.
SHE TYPES
Oh. er. Jonty. Got a sec?
Gerry. What's happening?
Well. I was hoping
you could tell me.
Go on.
It seems to me things are going
a bit crazy out there.
you know. Crazier than usual.
I mean...
..there's more drugs.
more ODs.
more...shooters.
Mm.
And every time
we want to go anywhere.
there's an OOB
stopping us from getting there.
We arrested an Op Gulliver
nominal the other week.
and he was sprung from the cell
before he even got
a wee visit from C3.
That's highly unusual.
wouldn't you say?
I just thought you could...
maybe tell me what's going on.
Nothing you need
to concern yourself with.
Is that right?
Yes. that is right...
Constable Cliff.
Thanks for the chat. sir.
You know. I was standing
on border checkpoints
while you were swotting
for your eleven-plus.
Is that right?
Look where that got you.
Dick.
All right. Columbo.
All those OOB orders
that you cross-referenced
with the exact times
of emergency calls...
..do you still have them.
or did you delete them
like I told you to?
Well. I...
Please tell me
you still have them.
Last week. the week before.
and the week before that.
It's like when a lot
of serious crimes happen.
somebody doesn't want us
anywhere near it.
I thought you said this was
just looking for trouble.
I also told you
that sometimes...
..trouble comes looking
for you.
Go and get the kids.
I can't believe this.
INDISTINCT CHATTER
Oh. you're joking me.
You going somewhere?
Oh. come on.
Oh. fuck.
What you did to my son
is child abuse.
And some day. mark my words.
you'll get
what's coming to you.
But you make sure
you tell your daddy this.
If you ever come near
my family again.
I will fucking kill you myself.
Get the...!
Siobhan...
ENGINE STARTS
Can't fight shadows. Grace.
You just can't.
Hiya.
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
What?
Your friend from work
has been here for hours.
I told her you were out.
but she insisted on waiting.
Who? Annie?
No. not Annie.
The other one.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today